Phone: (+98)9371434110 Tehran, Iran farzaadshojaei@gmail.com

Farzad Shojaei

QA Engineer

github.com/FarzaadShojaei linkedin.com/in/farzad-shojaei

SUMMERY

Each project has been a step toward excellence, showing that with the right attitude. With a background in both the technical and teamwork aspects of software projects with More than 100 thousands active users, Trying to Establish the Software Development Life Cycle (SDLC), Software Testing Life Cycle (STLC), and ISTQB standards with a close working relationship maintained with technical and product teams. Fostering a culture of open communication and mutual respect, This involved facilitating solution-oriented discussions with product visions.

SKILLS

• Cypress •JavaScript •Git •Postman •CI/CD •Jira

WORK EXPERIENCE

QA Engineer / Mofid Securities Tehran, Iran

January 2023 — Present

Mofid Securities is Iran's largest full-service stock brokerage firm leading private investment advisory with more that 10 million active Users.

- Identified team pain points and bottlenecks by meeting with tech leads and Product Owners, leading to a 40% increase in efficiency.
- Developed an RTM and Testing Checklist in Jira to enhance test coverage, resulting in a **50**% **reduction** in Android version releases based on OKR Reports.
- Implemented Automation and API Testing flows from scratch using **Cypress and Postman Tests** according to the Testing Checklist, saving **50**% of Acceptance testing time.
- Collaborated with the Infrastructure team to establish CI/CD processes in **Gitlab CI**, creating versioning workflows for applications and websites.

Software Tester / Panco.app

June 2021 — December 2022

Tehran,Iran

Pance.app The First Social Networking Platform in Iran with more than **100 thousand** active users per day, Focused on playing **mobile** games and Communicating alongside each other

- Resolved more than 80 vulnerabilities which led to enhancing system stability by 40% and reduced client-reported issues by 30% over six months
- Designed over 200 test cases and scenarios considering The testing checklist for **manual testing**. resulted in finding several critical crashes in games
- Achieved a 50% on-time delivery rate for projects through effective collaboration and accurate testing
- Monitored Continuously the impact of the changes through metrics and feedback.

EDUCATION

Bachelor Of Computer Engineering, *University of Science and Culture*

September 2019 - June 2023

LANGUAGES

English: Bilingual
French: Intermediate